{
"results" : [

  {
    "objectId": "6heXTqixCA",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "70hUkfhGmG"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Blaue oder rote Glasflaschen sollten im Braunglascontainer entsorgt werden?",
    "answer": "Nur Grünglas darf in geringen Mengen andersfarbige Partikel enthalten, ohne Recycling und Qualität zu beeinträchtigen.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-24T17:36:46.069Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-24T17:37:01.133Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "Ufy0VVtG26",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "70hUkfhGmG"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Blue or red glass bottles belong in the brown glass container?",
    "answer": "Only green glass may contain particles of a different color in small quantities without affecting recycling and quality.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-24T17:37:33.986Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-24T17:37:33.986Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "Tx9Hy34ux3",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "bPqwHtccWP"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Deckel von Glasflaschen sollten extra entsorgt werden?",
    "answer": "Metall- und Kunststoff¬deckel gehören in die Wert¬stoff¬tonne. Falls sie doch einmal im Altglascontainer landen, können sie durch  Sortier¬verfahren wieder rausgeholt werden.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-24T17:39:04.100Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T17:03:45.764Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "DtuHyvuG6S",
    "answer": "Metal and plastic lids belong in the recyclables garbage can. If they do end up in the glass container, they can be removed during the recycling process.",
    "question": "Lids of glass bottles should be disposed of separately?",
    "language_code": "en",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "bPqwHtccWP"
    },
    "createdAt": "2022-09-24T17:40:02.257Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T17:04:48.926Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "A6pguED7TG",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "uG5uAcfSKo"
    },
    "question": "Alle Altglascontainer werden sowieso in einem Fahrzeug ausgeleert?",
    "answer": "Der Container auf dem Entsorgungsfahrzeug besteht aus mehreren Kammern, in die das Glas – nach Farben sortiert – geleert wird.",
    "language_code": "de",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-24T17:41:40.267Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T17:02:37.304Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "BtvJJBEwa3",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "uG5uAcfSKo"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "All bottle banks are emptied in one vehicle?",
    "answer": "The container on the disposal vehicle consists of several chambers into which the glass - sorted by color - is emptied.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-24T17:42:31.986Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T17:02:44.335Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "5ebTankB9y",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "JE4bCMe12X"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Gekochtes Essensreste und Zitronenschalen dürfen in die Biotonne?",
    "answer": "Jegliche Art von Lebensmittel ist gutes „Futter“ für die Biogasanlage, auch hochkalorische und fettige Abfälle.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T07:25:47.860Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T17:01:52.726Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "u4hULdhBk8",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "JE4bCMe12X"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Cooked food scraps and lemon peels belong in the organic waste garbage can?",
    "answer": "Any type of food is good \" fodder\" for the biogas plant, including high-caloric and fatty waste.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T07:26:38.603Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T17:02:13.881Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "bsX67NDoln",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "nfTAEJhOIu"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Plastik und Bioplastik gehören nicht in die Biotonne?",
    "answer": "Die Anlagen können nicht dazwischen unterscheiden. Zudem zersetzt sich das Bioplastik zu langsam. In Form von Mikroplastik kann es in unseren Böden landen.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T07:27:15.797Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-25T07:27:15.797Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "8d8MtZQwXc",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "nfTAEJhOIu"
    },
    "question": "Plastic and bioplastics do not belong in the organic waste garbage can?",
    "answer": "The plants cannot distinguish between them. In addition, the bioplastics decompose too slowly. It can end up in our soil in the form of microplastics.",
    "language_code": "en",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T07:27:58.569Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-25T07:27:58.569Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "Pe7DE3fMan",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "tA466gE9lQ"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Papiertüten haben nichts in der Biotonne zu suchen?",
    "answer": "Allerdings können sie ohne Weiteres mit in die Biotonne geworfen werden, wenn darin Biogut gesammelt wird. Bitte darauf achten, dass sie keine Kunststoff-Innenbeschichtung haben.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T07:28:53.770Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-25T07:28:53.770Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "TsdC7yBuww",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "tA466gE9lQ"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Paper bags do not belong in the organic waste garbage can?",
    "answer": "However, they can be thrown into the organic waste garbage can without further ado if organic waste is collected in them. Please make sure that they do not have a plastic inner coating.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T07:29:35.140Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-25T07:29:35.140Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "6Xiy62UHIz",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "EHTIHS81GY"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Zerbrochenes Fensterglas und kaputte Getränkegläser gehören in den Restmüll?",
    "answer": "Diese Glasarten haben einen anderen Schmelzpunkt und müssen statt im Glas¬container im Restmüll entsorgt werden. Das gleich gilt für Keramik, Spiegel und Porzellan.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T09:26:49.152Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:59:33.412Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "v0GHkpBrmj",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "EHTIHS81GY"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Broken window glass and broken drinking glasses belong in the residual waste?",
    "answer": "These types of glass have a different melting point and must be disposed of in the residual waste instead of the glass container. The same applies to ceramics, mirrors and porcelain.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T09:27:38.002Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:59:49.765Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "8ELWB4zSVN",
    "question": "Am Ende wird sowieso alles zusammengekippt?",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "io8LBeasDg"
    },
    "answer": "Jede Abfallart geht einen anderen Entsorgungsweg. Mehr Informationen zu den Recyclingkreisläufen können auf den jeweiligen Seiten der Abfallarten gefunden werden.",
    "language_code": "de",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T09:38:16.219Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-25T09:38:16.219Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "G74MF9BnD8",
    "answer": "Each type of waste follows a different disposal route. More information about the recycling cycles can be found on the respective pages of the waste types.",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "io8LBeasDg"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "In the end, everything gets dumped in one place anyway?",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T09:38:58.959Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-09-25T09:38:58.959Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "lZStWJ2Cop",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "QreILdsATd"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Briefumschläge mit Fenster gehören in die Papiertonne?",
    "answer": "Solange der Briefumschlag überwiegend aus Papier besteht, darf er in die Papiertonne. Ein kleines Sichtfenster stört den Recyclingprozess dabei nicht.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T10:44:20.847Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:57:46.330Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "w4qIcHWiUm",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "QreILdsATd"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Envelopes with windows belong in the paper garbage can?",
    "answer": "As long as the envelope is mainly made of paper, it can go into the paper garbage can. A small viewing window does not interfere with the recycling process.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T10:45:16.592Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:57:47.646Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "8HxIeC8wNi",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "I62f1SHHfE"
    },
    "question": "Kassenbons gehören ins Altpapier?",
    "answer": "Kassenbons bestehen häufig aus sogenanntem Thermopapier. Dieses ist speziell beschichtet und kann nicht mit dem restlichen Papier verarbeitet werden.",
    "language_code": "de",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T10:46:15.021Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:56:14.121Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "TxuILtH4S6",
    "language_code": "en",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "I62f1SHHfE"
    },
    "question": "Receipts belong in the paper waste?",
    "answer": "Receipts are often made of so-called thermal paper. This is specially coated and cannot be recycled in the same way as normal paper.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T10:46:55.427Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:56:30.138Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "dNJ1Evq6oz",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "xzr67tv0Fg"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Leere Verpackungen müssen ausgewaschen werden?",
    "answer": "Das Säubern der Verpackungen passiert während des Recyclingprozesses. Es reicht daher, Verpackungen löffelrein restentleert zu entsorgen und unnötigen Wasserverbrauch zu vermeiden.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T13:29:46.195Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:55:30.343Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "Za17ggvejb",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "xzr67tv0Fg"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Empty packaging must be washed out?",
    "answer": "Cleaning of the packaging takes place during the recycling process. It is therefore sufficient to dispose of packaging emptied by spoon and to avoid unnecessary water consumption.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T13:31:12.232Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:55:35.490Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "GYhAxvRmrL",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "vOctGTSejI"
    },
    "language_code": "de",
    "question": "Nur ein Teil der Plastikverpackung wird recycelt?",
    "answer": "Manche Gegenstände besteht aus Mischkunststoff, der nicht oder nur schwer wieder getrennt werden kann.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T13:31:47.692Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:53:12.834Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "zV8ygauRhS",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "vOctGTSejI"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Only part of the plastic packaging is recycled?",
    "answer": "Some items are made of mixed plastic, which is impossible or difficult to separate again.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T13:32:42.032Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:53:25.543Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "fH3kjXkD1R",
    "question": "Verpackungen darf man nicht gestapelt entsorgen?",
    "language_code": "de",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "uqs3O5WAUK"
    },
    "answer": "Gestapelte Verpackungen unterschiedlicher Plastikarten können während des Recyclingprozesses nicht maschinell voneinander getrennt werden. Daher bitte nicht stapeln.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T13:33:20.523Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:51:50.875Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "fk6dswtAAR",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "uqs3O5WAUK"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Packaging should not be stacked before being thrown away?",
    "answer": "Stacked packaging of different plastic types cannot be separated from each other by machine during the recycling process. Therefore, please do not stack them.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-25T13:34:24.127Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:52:05.263Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "RTtrjz3rTq",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "vGnZqQiqCs"
    },
    "question": "Taschentücher dürfen nicht in die Papiertonne?",
    "answer": "Die Fasern von benutzten Taschentüchern sind sehr klein und meist stark verunreinigt.  Daher lieber in den Restmüll werfen, anstatt in die Papiertonne.",
    "language_code": "de",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-27T15:21:55.800Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:49:16.363Z"
  },
  {
    "objectId": "35529z6NE0",
    "category_myth_id": {
      "__type": "Pointer",
      "className": "CategoryMyth",
      "objectId": "vGnZqQiqCs"
    },
    "language_code": "en",
    "question": "Tissues are not allowed in the paper garbage can?",
    "answer": "The fibers of used handkerchiefs are very small and usually heavily contaminated.  Therefore, it is better to throw them in the residual waste instead of in the paper garbage can.",
    "createdAt": "2022-09-27T15:22:38.304Z",
    "updatedAt": "2022-10-13T16:49:36.439Z"
  }
]
}